Professional Experience

Full-stack JavaScript Web Developer **Freelancer,** Self-Employed 09/2020 - present | Lisbon, Portugal

Restaurant Manager, McDonald's 01/2017 - 08/2020 | Lisbon, Portugal

Food Quality and Safety Engineer, Casa Quintela 03/2015 - 08/2016 | Fundão, Portugal

Education

Full-stack JavaScript Web Developer,

Wild Code School

09/2020 - 02/2021 | Lisbon, Portugal

Primary Languages: Javascript

Environments: Node.JS

Frameworks / Libraries: React.js | Express.js |

Bootstrap | Scss Databases: MySQL

Others: SCRUM | Git | Github | HTML | CSS | Figma

l Miro

Exp: Client Projects | Working Remote

Biotechnology,

Universidade da Beira Interior 2010 - 2015 | Covilhã, Portugal

Projects

Krow.works.

React and Express (JavaScript) 🛮

11/2020 - present

Game App, React (JavaScript) □

11/2020 - 11/2020

Rick and Morty App, React (JavaScript) ☑

10/2020 - 11/2020

Interests

Practice Sports and Workout on Gym

Futsal and Judo

Current Learning

lava

Next Frameworks to Learn

React Native, Vue, and Redux



Luís Clara

Lisbon, Portugal

⊠ lc.sbg.92@gmail.com

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/luisclara/

https://github.com/LuisClara92

Profile

In the past few years, I have had a few different experiences related Biotechnology...

I recently changed my path, creating a new route for my future!

Why? Because after I started writing my 1st line of code, the feeling that I am doing something for the good of the community has become real!! I aim to be a full-stack developer with a lot of knowledge, strong skills.

Languages	
Portuguese	
English	
C	0.000
Hard S	KILLS
JavaScript	• • • • •
Git Ubuntu GitHub	••••
React Express Bootstrap Scss	• • • • •
Express.js	••••
MySQL	••••
Soft Skills	
Project Management	• • • •

Self learning **Troubleshooting Team Work**